(Leonard:)Did you guys see the paper
in The American Physics
Journal on supersolids?
(Leonard:)It's pretty interesting.
(Leonard:)This guy's working from
a hypothesis where...
(Raj:)Spoiler alert! Spoiler alert.
What? Don't ruin it for me, man.
(Raj:)I printed out a PDF
to read on the potty.
(Howard:)On the potty?
(Howard:)What are you, five?
(Raj:)It's a potty. What do you call it?
(Howard:)Toilet.
(Raj:)That's a little vulgar for
(Raj:)the dinner table, don't you think?
Oh, and "potty" is okay?
"Potty" is innocent.
"Potty" is adorable.
(Howard:)What do you do in the potty,
wee-wee?
(Raj:)If I don't have to boom-boom.
(Sheldon:)Greetings.
(Sheldon:)You all remember Amy Farrah Fowler.
Nice to see you. Hello.
(Sheldon:)Sorry we're late.
(Amy:)I must take responsibility.
(Amy:)I had to stop for
feminine hygiene supplies.
Aha. Okay.
(Sheldon:)I believe she's
experiencing her menses.
(Amy:)Actually, I'm not.
(Amy:)In order to avoid surprises,
I wear them all the time.
Aha. Okay.
"Toilet's" sounding
pretty good now, huh?
(Penny:)Hey, look, it's Shamy.
(Amy:)Shamy?